orbitalatk.com 2017-09-05

# Space Launch Vehicles

This Privacy Notice includes important information about your privacy in connection with your use of Orbital ATK websites. Please read it carefully. Your continued use of this website constitutes your agreement with this Privacy Notice and any subsequent updates.

**1\. TYPES OF INFORMATION COLLECTED**

**a. Personal Information Collected**

There may be areas on the Orbital ATK website where you can voluntarily share your personal information in order to satisfy the underlying transaction or purpose of your accessing the site. Personal information includes: name, company name, postal address, email address, phone number, social security number, zip code and the like. The information that you choose to provide will depend on the nature of your visit and the transaction that you seek to complete. 

**b. Children’s Policy**

The Orbital ATK website is not directed to, or designed for use by, children under the age of 13 years of age. Accordingly, Orbital ATK does not knowingly or intentionally solicit or collect information from children under 13 years of age. We ask that children not submit any personal information to us. 

**c. Cookies.**

Orbital ATK may collect information about you and your use of our site whenever you visit this site. For instance, when you request pages on our site, our servers automatically log your IP address. Your IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer whenever you are surfing the internet. This information is stored in server logs that we maintain and review for the purpose of improving and supporting the secure operation of our website. Orbital ATK may use cookies for tracking or to make the site easier to use. A cookie is a small amount of data that is transferred to your browser by a web server. With most internet browsers, you can take steps to limit tracking. You can set your browser to block all cookies or warn you before a cookie is stored. Enabling cookies allows you to take full advantage of all the features on the site and if you disable cookies your experience with our web site may be degraded. 

In some instances, Orbital ATK may use tracking scripts or “tracers” that recognize a unique identifier from a cookie placed on your hard drive by another website. These are used by Orbital ATK solely to gauge the success of our own advertising. For instance, we may use a tracer to determine whether you visit certain web pages where Orbital ATK may have placed a banner ad. We do not use tracers to gather information on your use of the internet unrelated to Orbital ATK. Please note that Orbital ATK does not use tracers to identify your personal information. 

**2\. USE OF INFORMATION COLLECTED.**

Orbital ATK will use the personal Information directly submitted by you for the purpose for which you have provided it, whether it be to apply for a job, request information, etc. If you are a supplier you may be asked to identify the financial institution you use and provide account numbers. Orbital ATK may also use the information you provide to us to contact you for reasons related to your original communication to us. Your e-mail address is not used for any other purpose except to the extent necessary to follow-up on a specific question. Visitors who give us their telephone numbers online will only receive telephone contact from us for reasons related to the visitor’s original communication or request. The specific information that you may choose to provide will depend on the nature of the transaction to be completed and is always voluntary. We may use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our website.

**3\. SHARING OF PERSONAL INFORMATION**

Orbital ATK will not sell, rent, share, monitor, edit, or disclose any personal information about you. Orbital ATK may share your personal information with third parties assisting us in processing a transaction requested by you. In some cases we may share the information with service providers retained by the Corporation to provide services on its behalf. From whatever place you provide information to this website, you should expect that it will be processed and viewed in the United States. Your use of this website constitutes your consent for any cross-border data transfer resulting from such use. Your information may also be used or shared for reasons such as: (i) to comply with legal process or other legal requirements of any governmental authority; (ii) in connection with investigations or other effort to prevent illegal activities or pertaining to public safety; (iii) to protect and defend the rights or property of Orbital ATK; (iv) to enforce this Privacy Policy; (v) with vendors operating on our behalf or (vi) to operate or conduct maintenance and repair of the site or equipment.

**4\. PROTECTION OF PERSONAL INFORMATION**

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the safe use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the personal information we collect. 

**6\. OTHER LIMITS TO YOUR PRIVACY**

This website may contain links to other non-Orbital ATK websites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites. We have no control over the use of such websites and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose any personal information on these websites.

**7\. UPDATES AND CHANGES TO PRIVACY POLICY**

We reserve the right, at any time and without notice, to add to, change, update or modify this Privacy Policy, simply by posting such change, update or modification on the site. Any such change, update or modification will be effective immediately upon posting on the site. Updates and changes to the Terms and Conditions and the Privacy Policy will continue to govern your use of the site even if you do not acknowledge such changes.
